Guide to the System Development Foundation (Palo Alto, Calif.) Records, 1957-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series 2. Research Program Files
  - Subseries A. Grants Awarded
    - Subsubseries 2. Grant Program files
      - A. Grant Administration files
        - G242d, Site visit material, Jan. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
        - G242d, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - G242d, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
        - G242c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - G242c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
        - G242b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
        - G242b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
        - G242a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
        - G242a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
        - G242a, Background information #1 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - G242a, Background information #2 (Box 10, Folder 15)
        - G242a, Background information #3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - G243b, Grant administration and correspondnece, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - G243a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - G243a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - G243a, Background information (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - G244, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - G244, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - G244, Proposal, Mar. 1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - G245, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - G245, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 10)
        - G246b, Grant administration and correspondence,1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
        - G246b, Grant administration and correspondence,1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - G246a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1985, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 13)
        - G246a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - G246, Proposal drafts and SDF notes on robotics, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
        - G247, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
        - G247, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        - G247, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - G247, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - G247, Background information #1 (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - G247, Background information #2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - G248b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - G248b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 12, Folder 9)
        - G248a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - G248a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        - G248a, Background information (Box 12, Folder 12)
        - G249g, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 13)
        - G249f, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
        - G249e, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 15)
        - G249c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
        - G249c, Grant administration and correspondence, May-Dec. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - G249c, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - G249c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 and c. 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - G249[a,b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - G249 [a,b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - G249 [a,b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - G249 [a,b], Background information, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
        - G249[a,c], Site visit material, Part IMar. 1987 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - G249 [a,c], Site visit materials, Part IIMar. 1987 (Box 13, Folder 9)
        - G249 [a,c], Site visit materials, Parts III and IVMar. 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
        - G255d, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
        - G255c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
        - G255b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
        - G255a, Grant administration and correspondence, Apr.-Dec. 1983, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
        - G255a, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar. 1983 #1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
        - G255a, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar. 1983 #2 (Box 14, Folder 1)
        - G255a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-Feb. 1983 (Box 14, Folder 2)
        - G255a, Background information (Box 14, Folder 3)
        - G257, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
        - G275, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
        - G275, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
        - G275, Background information #1 (Box 14, Folder 7)
        - G275, Background information #2 (Box 14, Folder 8)
        - G275, Background information #3 (Box 14, Folder 9)
        - G276, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
        - G276, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
        - G276, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 12)
        - G276, Background information (Box 15, Folder 1)
        - G277, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        - G283c, Grant administration and correspondence, July 1986-1988 (Box 15, Folder 3)
        - G283c, Grant administration and correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
        - G283c, Grant administration and correspondence, Aug.-Oct. 1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
        - G283c, University-approved proposal, June 1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
        - G283c, Proposal, June 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
        - G283c, Preliminary materials, June 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
        - G283b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 15, Folder 9)
        - G283b, Grant administration and correspondence, Dec. 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
        - G283b, Grant administration and correspondence, Nov. 1983 (Box 15, Folder 11)
        - [R] G283b, Grant administration and correspondence, c. Nov. or Dec. 1983 (Box 15, Folder 12)
        - G283b, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Oct. 1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
        - G283b, Grant administration and correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1982 (Box 15, Folder 14)
        - G283a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
        - G283a, Background information (Box 16, Folder 2)
        - G285c Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
        - G285b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
        - G285b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
        - G285a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        - G293, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981-1983, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 7)
        - G297, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
        - G297, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 9)
        - G301, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 10)
        - G301, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
        - G303, Grant administration and correspondence, May 1987-June 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
        - G303, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
        - G303, Grant administration and correspondence, July-Nov. 1984 (Box 16, Folder 14)
        - G303, Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 15)
        - G303, Project summary, Dec. 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
        - G303, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.-Dec. 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
        - G303, Grant proposal, Section I-VIMar. 4, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 3)
        - G303, Grant proposal, Appendix AMar. 4, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
        - G303, Grant proposal, Appendices B-EMar. 4, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
        - G303, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
        - G303, Background information #1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
        - G303, Background information #2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
        - G303, Background information #3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        - G303, Background information #4 (Box 17, Folder 10)
        - G303, Background information #5 (Box 17, Folder 11)
        - G303, Background information #6 (Box 17, Folder 12)
        - G303, Background information #7 (Box 17, Folder 13)
        - G305b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 14)
        - G305b, Grant administration and correspondence, May 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 15)
        - [NOTE: This grant is related to G524.] (Box 18)
        - G305b, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
        - G305b, Grant proposal, drafts, Mar. 1983 (Box 18, Folder 2)
        - G305b, Grant proposal, drafts, Feb. 12, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 3)
        - G305b, Background information #1 (Box 18, Folder 4)
        - G305b, Background information #2 (Box 18, Folder 5)
        - G305a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
        - G313c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 7)
        - G313b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 8)
        - G313b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
        - G313b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 10)
        - G313b, University acknowledgements of grant payments, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
        - G313a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 12)
        - G313a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        - G313a, Background information (Box 18, Folder 14)
        - G314a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 18, Folder 15)
        - G314a, Proposal attachments #1 (Box 18, Folder 16)
        - G314a, Proposal attachments #2 (Box 18, Folder 17)
        - G314a, Proposal attachments #3 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        - G314a, Proposal attachments #4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        - G314a, Proposal attachments #5 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        - G314a, Materials from preliminary site visit, Dec. 1982 (Box 19, Folder 4)
        - G318, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-83, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        - G327g, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        - G327g, Transferring the Language of Data Project to Princeton: Working file of the SDF Director of Program Administration, May-June 1987 (Box 19, Folder 7)
        - G327g, Transfering the Language of Data Project to Princeton: Working file of the SDF Director of Program Administration, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        - G327g, "Deliverables," 1986 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        - [R] G327g, Financial reports and review, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 10)
        - G327f, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 11)
        - G327f, Arranging details of grant under new principal investigator,1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
        - G327f, Additional information on research subject, c. 1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
        - G327e, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 14)
        - G327e, Grant administration and correspondence, Oct.-Dec. 1985 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        - G327e, Site visit notes and materials, Sep.-Oct. 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
        - G327e, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Sep. 1985 (Box 19, Folder 17)
        - G327e-, Background information (Box 19, Folder 18)
        - G327d, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        - G327c, Financial and annual reports, 1985-1987 (Box 20, Folder 2)
        - G327c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        - G327c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
        - G327c, Background information #1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
        - G327c, Background information #2 (Box 20, Folder 6)
        - G327c, Background information #3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        - G327c, Background information #4 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        - G327b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        - G327b, Grant administration and correspondence, c.1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        - G327a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        - G327b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 12)
        - G327[a-d], Progress report, draft, July 1985 (Box 20, Folder 13)
        - G327, Letters from John W. Tukey, Feb.-Mar. 1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
        - G327, "A computational formalism for information systems," by Henson Graves and David Posner, c. Nov. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 15)
        - G327[a or b], Letter accompanying grant payment, Aug. 1982 (Box 20, Folder 16)
        - G337c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 20, Folder 17)
        - G337[a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 18)
        - G337 [a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, Mar. 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
        - G337 [a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1981-Feb. 1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
        - G337 [a-b], Background information (Box 21, Folder 3)
        - G341, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 4)
        - G341, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 5)
        - G341, Background information (Box 21, Folder 6)
        - G344, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
        - G344, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
        - G345[a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
        - G345 [a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 10)
        - G345 [a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 11)
        - G345 [a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 12)
        - G345 [a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
        - G346, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
        - G346, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
        - G346, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
        - G346, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 17)
        - G346, Background information (Box 22, Folder 1)
        - G347, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 2)
        - G348d, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 3)
        - G348d, Grant administration and correspondence, July-Nov. 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
        - G348c, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
        - G348c, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.-Dec. 1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
        - G348c, Site visit package, Parts 1-3Feb. 28, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
        - G348c, Site visit package, Part 4 - BacknotesFeb. 28, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 8)
        - G348b, Grant administration and correspondence, May 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
        - G348b, University of Utah Dextrous Hand. Slides. Oct. 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
        - G348b, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
        - G348a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
        - G348a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
        - G348a, Grant administration and correspondence, June-Dec. 1982 (Box 22, Folder 14)
        - G348a, Proposal drafts, May 1982 (Box 22, Folder 15)
        - G348a, Background information (Box 22, Folder 16)
        - G348, University acknowledgements of grant payments, 1983-1985 (Box 22, Folder 17)
        - G349, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 18)
        - G350, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 22, Folder 19)
        - G350, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 20)
        - G350, Background information: Typeworld, Apr. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        - G350, Background information: The Computer Modern Family of Typfaces, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
        - G351b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
        - G351b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 4)
        - G351b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
        - G351a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
        - G351a, Annual report, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 7)
        - G351a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
        - G351a, Grant administration and correspondence, May-Sep. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 9)
        - G351a, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
        - G351a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 11)
        - G351a, Computer music outlines, c.1981 or 1983 (Box 23, Folder 12)
        - G357, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 13)
        - G357, Grant administration and correspondence, May-Aug. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 14)
        - G357, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1982 (Box 23, Folder 15)
        - G358, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 23, Folder 16)
        - G358, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 17)
        - G358, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 18)
        - G359d, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.1987-June 1988 (Box 23, Folder 19)
        - G359b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 1)
        - G359b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
        - G359a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
        - G359a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 4)
        - G359a, Grant administration and correspondence, May-Dec., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 5)
        - G359a, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.-Apr., 1982 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        - G359a, Revised proposal, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
        - G359a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
        - G362, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 24, Folder 9)
        - G380e, Grant administration and correspondence, Apr.-June 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
        - G380e, Grant administration and correspondence, Apr.-Oct. 1987 (Box 24, Folder 11)
        - G380d, Grant administration and correspondence, May 1987-June 1988 (Box 24, Folder 12)
        - G380d, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.-Sep. 1986 (Box 24, Folder 13)
        - G380d, Progress report and proposal for continuation, June 1986 (Box 24, Folder 14)
        - G380d, Site visit material: reprints, June 1986 (Box 24, Folder 15)
        - G380b, Grant administration and correspondence, May 1987, Apr.-June 1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
        - G380b, Report to trustees of SDF, Sep. 1985 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        - G380[a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 24, Folder 18)
        - G380[a-c], Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 24, Folder 19)
        - G380[a-c], Grant administration and correspondence, May-Dec. 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
        - G380[a-c], Grant administration and correspondence,Apr. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - G380[a-c], Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Mar. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - [R] G380[a-c], Early notes, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - G380[a-c], Proposal attachments #1, Feb. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - G380[a-c], Proposal attachments #2, Feb. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - G389b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - G389b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - G389b, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - G389a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - G389a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - G389a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - G389a, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - G402, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - G402, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar.-Dec. 1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - G402, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, Sep. 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 2)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-Aug. 1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 4)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, July-Dec. 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-May 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, Apr.-Sep. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 7)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, Mar. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
        - G403, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 9)
        - G407, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 26, Folder 10)
        - G407, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
        - G407, Grant administration and correspondence, Apr. - Dec. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 12)
        - G407, Additions to proposal, Mar. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 13)
        - G407, Grant administration and correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1983 (Box 26, Folder 14)
        - G416[a-b], Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 26, Folder 15)
        - G444, Grant administration and correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 27, Folder 1)
        - G456, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1983, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 2)
        - G458, Grant administration and correspondence, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 3)
        - G458, Background information #1 (Box 27, Folder 4)
        - G458, Background information #2 (Box 27, Folder 5)
        - G458, Background information #3 (Box 27, Folder 6)
        - G460k, Grant administration and correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
        - G460j, Grant administration and correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 8)
        - G460i, Grant administration and correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
        - G460g, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 10)
        - G460f, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
        - G460e, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984-1987 (Box 27, Folder 12)
        - G460d, Grant administration and correspondence, 1984, 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 13)